<resources>
    <string name="app_name">10DaysOfPatapon</string>
    <string name="hatapon_name">Hatapon</string>
    <string name="hatapon_description">Hatapon is the most important Patapon that you encounter in all three games and functions to hold the army together and lead them; however, he can\'t attack. He holds the Patapon banner with an owl on the top. He has only a tiny HP of 200. His death immediately results in a mission failure. His family was given the ability to lead the army. "Hata" (旗) means "flag" in Japanese.</string>
    <string name="yaripon_name">Yaripon</string>
    <string name="yaripon_description">"Yaripons throw spears to attack. They have no shield and are bad at close combat, but are good for attacking medium ranged targets. They're pretty good for hunting because they don’t scare the animals away by getting too close. In the first and second Patapon games, the Yaripon unit is the first unit you meet (apart from Hatapon) and you will have three Yaripons to become your first army. You might want to have some close combat units to protect your Yaripons. In Patapon 3, Yaripon is in the class of 'Yarida'. \"Yari\" (槍) means \"spear\" in Japanese. "</string>
    <string name="dayNumber">Day %1$s</string>
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">See more or less information about this patapon</string>
    <string name="tatepon_name">Tatepon</string>
    <string name="tatepon_description">An excellent and well-defenced Patapon. They can wield Axes or Swords and Shields. They are bad at hunting; in fact, they cannot really hunt at all, because they are close-range units. They must get very close to their targets, which makes the hunted creatures runs away. In Fever, their shields enlarge when you use the ChakaChaka song. A full Tatepon squad consists of 6 Tatepons. \"Tate\" (盾) means \"shield\" in Japanese.</string>
    <string name="yumipon_name">Yumipon</string>
    <string name="yumipon_description">Bow-wielding Patapons. These Patapons have one of the largest attack range in the games (wind can increase or decrease the range of their attack depending on which way it is blowing). If the Tailwind Juju is activated, the range of Yumipons will be dramatically increased. While they are extremely effective and can rain down arrows on enemies from afar, they are vulnerable to fire. While in Fever or Charge up (PonChaka), they fire three arrows at once. A full Yumipon squad consists of 6 Yumipons. \"Yumi\" (弓) means \"bow\" in Japanese.</string>
    <string name="kibapon_name">Kibapon</string>
    <string name="kibapon_description">The Patapon tribe\'s cavalry unit. Equipped with horses and halberds, Kibapons deal heavy damage and knock back enemy troops. While relatively useless normally, their speed and knockback greatly increase in Fever. They should only be used by a skilled player. A full Kibapon squad consists of 3 Kibapons. If you\'re not good at keeping Fever or charging, don\'t use these units. Kibapons can also equip a variety of different horses as well as halberds. \"Kiba\" (騎馬) means \"horse-rider\" in Japanese.</string>
    <string name="dekapon_name">Dekapon</string>
    <string name="dekapon_description">Large mace-wielding Patapon. These monstrous brutes are extremely large and bulky and as a result, they do massive damage to their targets. They also have very high HP. Unfortunately, Dekapons are slow, making them easily targeted by wide-range attacks. If using PonChaka~PonPon, Dekapons activates NoshiNoshizugan, a ground slam attack that creates an earthquake and stuns enemies. A full Dekapon squad consists of 3 Dekapons. \"Deka\" is actually a shortened form of \"dekai\" (でかい), which means \"Gargantuan\" in Japanese.</string>
    <string name="megapon_name">Megapon</string>
    <string name="megapon_description">Megapons are by far the oddest unit in the games. They are taller than most other Patapons, and carry around massive horns. They appear to smile all the time, even when enemies are around, and even as they die. They frown when you miss a beat or when they fall asleep/catch fire. When they attack, they play their horns and the soundwaves/sonic balls that are projected take on physical form, flying at the enemy and causing damage. Megapons have a variety of attacks, but the three most utilized are a wave of 3 blue notes that bounce off of and around the enemy, causing ricochet damage, a massive red note only used during Fever Mode that pierces and hits multiple times, causing massive damage, and a giant green note that is only used when you use PonChaka~ChakaChaka. Unlike most Patapon units, their name has no Japanese origin, but is instead a pun of \"megaphone\".</string>
    <string name="toripon_name">Toripon</string>
    <string name="toripon_description">A bird-riding Patapon. They use javelins, much like theYaripons\' spears. Their attacks are similar to Yaripons\'. During fever, they throw three javelins when attacking. They provide excellent air support and as long as you keep the rhythm going, they cannot be affected by melee attacks. They are extremely effective units when fighting bosses with no air attacks, like Garuru. Also, they are great when facing Karmen fortresses - as long as you can keep the enemy Yarimen and Yumimen busy. A full Toripon squad consists of 3 Toripons. \"Tori\" (鳥) means \"bird\" in Japanese.</string>
    <string name="robopon_name">Robopon</string>
    <string name="robopon_description">Robopons are powerful robotic melee units that fight with their extraordinarily large robotic arms. They can do relatively high damage, and have decent defense but can take damage. If using PonChaka~PonPon, they will throw big rocks. Each Robopon will throw 1 rock. A full Robopon squad consists of 3 Robopons. Robopons are one of the most powerful units. Like Megapons, \"robo\" has no Japanese meaning. Instead it is originated from the word \"robot\", which explains their robotic arms.</string>
    <string name="mahopon_name">Mahopon</string>
    <string name="mahopon_description">The Patapon tribe\'s spellcasters. They wields a variety of staffs or scepters and wears boots. Mahopons are frail, but are able to perform a variety of duties for the team. Unlike most Patapon units, the Mahopons\' abilities change depending on what staff they currently wield. A full Mahopon squad consists of 3 Mahopons. There are approximately 11 Mahopon magic spells with a wide variety of effects, like: restoring HP; cure status effects, boosting defenses, causing explosions, fire or thunderstorms, summoning hails of meteors, etc. \"Maho\" (魔) means \"spell\" in Japanese.</string>
    <string name="top_bar_title">10 DAYS OF</string>

</resources>